* 

    Help Israel’s People
    
    Support Israel as the war with Hamas continues. 

    Follow Yael on Instagram
    
    Keep up with Yael Eckstein as she helps Jews around the world.

    Send A Blessing
    
    Show her she isn’t alone with your best gift today.

    Stay Connected
    
    Get updates on breaking news, ways to get involved, and the impact of your support.

    Inspiration in Your Inbox
    
    Sign up for reflections and insights on Israel and the Jewish faith.

    Join Bishop Lanier
    
    Stand with Bishop Lanier in supporting Israel with your best gift today.

1. [Home](https://www.ifcj.org/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

The Fellowship considers stewardship of our supporters and their privacy a top priority. This Privacy Policy was created to give you confidence regarding our responsible stewardship of your information. In addition to this Privacy Policy, we are ensuring all data that is submitted on our website is secure and adheres to industry compliance standards. Thank you for your continued partnership in this ministry – we couldn’t strengthen Israel and her people without you.

**Contents**

**I. General Statement and General Privacy Policy for Visitors to our Site**

**II. Donor-Specific Privacy**

**III. How to Contact Us**

**I. General Statement and General Privacy Policy for Visitors to our Site**

Each time you use the IFCJ website, the current version of the Privacy Policy applies. By visiting www.ifcj.org, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the processes and polices outlined in this Privacy Policy and consent to our data collection and usage practices.

This Privacy Policy applies to the collections, uses, and disclosures of personal information by International Fellowship of Christians and Jews (“IFCJ” or “we”) in connection with the International Fellowship of Christians and Jews‘ website (“the website”). This policy also applies when you use social media that overlaps IFCJ’s own social media or where your use of social media overlaps this site.

All personal information collected at this site kept strictly confidential. We collect and utilize your non-personal data to provide you with a better experience through the IFCJ website and Internet promotions and utilize your personal data, provided you give consent, to mail, call, email, or provide direct communications through other means (the “Purposes”) and as required or permitted by applicable law.

Personal information is not be sold, rented, or loaned, other than to third-party service providers engaged to help us carry out the Purposes which are bound by agreement to protect your personal information; as required or permitted by law; to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual sale, merger, amalgamation, or any other type of transfer affecting IFCJ in order for you to continue to receive the same products and services from the third party; or to such other parties to which you may consent from time to time. Personal information may be shared with trusted organizations.

If you do submit information to us, we will use that information for the purposes for which it was submitted and by providing it, you are consenting to such use. You may withdraw consent with how we use your personal information, subject to reasonable notice. If you wish to withdraw your consent at any time, please contact Donor Relations. (see “How to Contact Us” below). We will inform you of the implications of withdrawing consent.

This policy will be updated periodically, so please be sure to reread it from time to time. By submitting your personal information to us, you are agreeing that IFCJ may use the information in accordance with this Policy. If you provided personal information under an older version of this Policy, please be advised that this Policy applies to you and supersedes any previous Policy.

**A. Protecting Your Privacy**

The Privacy Policy is current as of the “last updated” date which appears on this page. Examples of the Purposes for which we collect, use, and disclose personal information via the website are set out below. We recommend you review this Privacy Policy periodically. From time to time, we may make changes to this Privacy Policy with or without notice to you. We will treat personal information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**B. What is Personal Information?**

Personal information is any information that is identifiable to you. This information may include but is not limited to your name, personal mailing address, personal phone numbers, and personal email address. Personal information, however, does not include your business name, business title, business address, and business telephone number in your capacity as an employee of an organization.

**C. How IFCJ Uses Your Information**

· To process and respond to inquiries and for the purposes for which you provided the information, such as to process donations, register or renew you as a member, purchase merchandise, or receive information about a project.

· To personalize the content and improve the navigability of the website.

· To alert you to new projects, site features, special events, and services.

· To conduct surveys to measure your satisfaction with our service.

· To personalize the content you see on both our website and other Fellowship promotions.

· To provide you with personalized mail, calls, emails, or other direct communications, provided you give your consent.

· To enforce our Terms of Use.

IFCJ complies with those provisions of the CAN-SPAM Act applicable to charitable organizations. All emails sent contain a link to unsubscribe from IFCJ email. You may subscribe or unsubscribe to IFCJ at any time by contacting IFCJ or by giving a notice by United States mail or email to the address provided at the end of this policy.

**D. Browser Information Collected on the Site and Advertising**

The website collects statistical information through a log file. This generates a monthly report that indicates which pages were visited and how frequently, referring pages, and IP addresses. Individual identities cannot be determined from these reports. The developers of this site use and disclose this information, including your IP address, to help us develop further content and features for the site. We use third parties to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. These parties may collect information about your visits to certain web pages on our site and may use technology such as cookies and web beacons. The data collected is reported back to us, and we may link this information to personal information we have concerning you. This information allows us to track which other websites have linked visitors to our site, and what pages of our site are used by and are of interest to those visitors so that we may better advertise our mission, program, and events.

**E. Privacy Policies of Other Sites**

Our website provides links to many other sites. Some of these sites may use cookies to collect personal information or commercial data. IFCJ is not responsible for the privacy practices of sites to which it links, and advises you to review the privacy policies of those sites when visiting such sites.

**F. Use of Cookies**

Our site may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our site. Cookies are pieces of information that some websites transfer to the computer that is browsing that website and are used for record-keeping purposes at many websites. Use of cookies makes web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular website, and making sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly.

If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function properly when you view them.

**G. “Do Not Track” Signals**

Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites, web applications, and services that you do not want them to track your online activities. The website does not have the ability to honor “Do Not Track” signals.

**H. Tell a Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site, we ask for the friend’s name and email address. IFCJ will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. IFCJ does not capture the information of the friends you refer

to our site unless and until they provide their consent to our collection of their personal information.

**I. Security**

All information provided to IFCJ is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption that has been certified by Sectigo, the world’s largest commercial Certificate Authority (CA). SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser encrypt data that is submitted via IFCJ’s website. While no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure, we take every precaution and strive for the highest standard of security to protect your information.

**J. European Union Citizens**

European Union citizens have certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), including the following:

· Right to be informed. You have the right to know whether your personal information is being processed.

· Right of access. You have the right to obtain copy of what is being processed.

· Right to rectification. When personal information is inaccurate, you have the right to a process to correct the information.

· Right to erasure of your personal information (the “right to be forgotten”).

· Right to restrict processing. You have the right to limit the processing of your personal information.

· Right to data portability. You have the right to receive personal information concerning you and the right to have that information transmitted from us to a controller where technically feasible.

· Right to object. You have the right to object to the processing of your personal information, including information processed for direct marketing purposes.

· Rights related to automated decision making and profiling. You have the right to not be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing.

If you are an EU citizen, you can exercise your rights by contacting our Data Privacy Officer at [\[email protected\]](https://www.ifcj.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**K. Children’s Data**

IFCJ does not knowingly gather any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. You must be 13 years of age or older to access the site.

**L. Data Retention**

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal

data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

**M. Your Legal Rights**

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data. You have the right to:

Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.

Limit processing of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your situation which makes you want to object to processing. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, there may be overriding grounds which require us to process your information.

Request we provide your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

Withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any process carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you.

**II. Donor-Specific Privacy**

As a donor submitting personally identifying information (“Personal Donor Information”) to us or any of our staff, you consent to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy and to our processing and use of Personal Donor Information for the purposes stated below.

**A. Personal Donor Information**

“Personal Donor Information” is information that identifies you personally as a donor to IFCJ, such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address. We collect and store the personally identifiable information that you have provided us via one of the email addresses identified on our website or when you otherwise contact us in person, by phone or email, to volunteer. We collect your name, email address and other contact

information if you register for an event. We also collect your name, email address, telephone number, and payment information when you contribute, either on our website, at a special event, over the phone or by mailing in a check. The above list provides a sample of Personal Donor Information that may be collected by IFCJ. From time to time, we may collect personal information from you in ways not described above.

**B. Use and Disclosure of Personal Donor Information**

· We only rent or exchange lists we maintain that may include your Personal Donor Information (excluding any payment or other similar secure data), collected on the website or through any other activities, with other third parties we believe engage in activities that are not inconsistent with the mission and core beliefs of IFCJ. You may opt out of having your Personal Donor Information shared by us by following the process described in our general Privacy Policy.

· We will not send you mailings on behalf of other organizations.

· We will collect payment information, billing address, and other information necessary to process a donation, volunteer registration, or event registration.

· We will use your information to comply with the law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on us.

· We will use Personal Donor Information to protect against potential fraud. We may verify with third parties the information collected in the course of processing a gift, event registration, or other donation. If you use a credit or debit card on the website, we may use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to us and that the card being used has not been reported lost or stolen.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy or at the time we request the information, we do not otherwise disclose your Personal Donor Information to any third parties.

**III. How to Contact Us**

All comments, questions, concerns, or requests, including access requests, regarding your personal information or our Privacy Policy and practices, should be forwarded to as follows:

In writing:

International Fellowship of Christians and Jews

303 East Wacker Drive, Suite 2300

Chicago, IL 60601

Tel: (800) 486-8844

Or send an e-mail to: [\[email protected\]](https://www.ifcj.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). IFCJ has appointed a data privacy officer to oversee compliance and enforcement of this Privacy Policy. Your contact through this process will be sent to that officer.

Stay Connected

Stay informed about issues affecting Israel, the Jewish people, Jewish-Christian relations, receive daily devotionals, and more.

Sign Up for Text Updates

Get text messages sent directly to your phone to stay up-to-date on The Fellowship’s life-saving work in Israel and around the world.

Subscribe to Our Newsletter

Stay informed about issues affecting Israel, the Jewish people, and Jewish-Christian relations, receive Daily Devotionals and more.

Subscribe to Our Newsletter

Stay informed about issues affecting Israel, the Jewish people, Jewish-Christian relations, receive daily devotionals, and more.

Who We Are

Who We Help

Latest News

Learn

Act

Ways to Give

© 2024 International Fellowship of Christians and Jews®  
303 East Wacker Drive, Suite 2300,  
Chicago, IL 60601-5224  
[800-486-8844](tel:800-486-8844) The Fellowship IFCJ

A 501(c)(3) tax-exempt, non-profit organization.  
_The Fellowship_’s tax identification number is 36-3256096.
